

CONTACTS



m.meinarts10@gmail.com



+447575827773 +37120069167









LANGUAGES

- Russian Native
- English C1+

SKILLS / WORKED WITH

- React
- Redux / Redux toolkit
- JS/ES6/Typescript
- Redux-Thunk, Formik
- Rest API, Axios
- Material UI, Ant-D
- Styled Components
- Storybook, Postman, **TDD**
- HTML, HTML5
- CSS, SASS
- Git, Github

MAKSS MEINARTS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hello, I'm a front-end developer from Latvia who has experience in creating SPA. My main stack is React, Redux & Typescript. But I'm always keen on learning new stacks. I would like to learn Node.js or another backend framework to expand my abilities for building applications

EDUCATION

2021 - Present

IT-INCUBATOR

Front-end developer

2018 - 2019

PROFESSIONAL COOKERY

Edinburgh College

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - Present

FREELANCE

- Building custom components
- Creating form validations
- Fixing bugs
- Creating unit tests
- Building custom storybook components
- Creating responsive layouts

2022 - Present

CARDS APP

• Me and my team created SPA, like Anki using React, Typescript and Redux for a state manager. This application allows you to browse through or create new packs to help you memorize things faster. You can follow the progress on Github: repository view project